Soul Men is a comedy, music film directed by Malcolm D. Lee.
Two former backup soul singers, Louis and Floyd, have not spoken to each other in 20 years, and reluctantly agree to
travel across the country together to a reunion concert to honor their recently-deceased lead singer.
Cleo, a beautiful young woman who is believed to be Floyd's
daughter, accompanies them as a new singer.
Louis Hinds, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Floyd Henderson, played by Bernie Mac.
Cleo, played by Sharon Leal.
Phillip, played by Adam Herschman.
Danny Epstein, played by Sean Hayes.
Lester, played by Affion Crockett.
Soul Men is a 2008 American musical comedy film directed by Malcolm D.
Lee, and starring Samuel L.
Jackson, Bernie Mac, Sharon Leal and Sean Hayes.
The film released on November 7, 2008.
It was one of three films featuring Mac that were released after his death (and was actually
released on the same date as another posthumous film, Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa).
distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.
Mac and Isaac Hayes died on August 9 and 10, 2008,
respectively, and the film is dedicated to their memory.
Director Lee said the film was heavily re-edited to soften the
tone of the film, as a tribute to the two actors.
Critical reviews were mixed, and the film was financially unsuccessful.
The tone is lighthearted.